(Love In Sync)
(Kim Myung Soo)
(Kang Min Ah)
(Love In Sync)
(All people, incidents, and backgrounds...)
(in this drama are fictitious and unrelated to reality.)
(Also, children and animals were filmed under production guidelines.)
Ji An.
Are you okay?
Why are you out here in the cold?
Is something wrong?
Are you okay?
Are you hurt?
Then what is wrong?
I'm sorry.
What is it? What's wrong?
Tell me.
How did you end up in a place like this?
I wasn't expecting a tearful reunion,
but still,
I wasn't expecting to be treated this coldly.
Aren't you even curious how I've been all this time?
Have you...
been well?
How could I have been?
A child can leave the nest and live well,
but a parent...
can't do that so easily.
Can you still...
not be alone when it rains?
It started after that accident when you were a child, right?
You started trembling every time it rained.
Because of you, even when I was in the US,
whenever I heard it was raining in Korea,
I would get so worried.
You...
will never understand how a mother feels.
The person who saved me from that accident...
Was it really you?
Kiddo, stay with me. Kiddo.
Sweetie, are you awake?
Thank goodness.
My baby.
Mommy was so worried.
What about the man?
A man?
A man saved me.
He promised he would save me.
My poor baby, you must have been dreaming.
- No, I saw him. - It was me.
I'm the one who found you, Ji An.
You were the one who saved me?
Of course. I'm your mother.
If it wasn't me...
besides me, your mother,
who would risk their life for you?
Right?
You're lying.
How long were you going to lie to me?
You weren't the one who saved me that day.
So you remember it all.
Why did you lie about it?
- Why? - It was for you.
Not for yourself?
To a seven-year-old child,
how could I say that someone died trying to save you?
Especially when...
the accident happened because of you.
Hey, kid,
this is a very dangerous scene to film.
- It's not that simple... - I still want to do it.
I can do it.
If you hadn't been so stubborn that day,
the accident wouldn't have happened,
and that man wouldn't have died saving you.
But what mother in the world...
could tell her own child such a cruel truth?
That man, Cha Eun Hwan...
He doesn't know about this yet, does he?
Good.
He must never find out.
How devastated would he be?
His own father died because of you.
My daughter,
it has been hard for you without me, hasn't it?
You do not have to worry anymore.
Your mother is here now.
("Yu Ji An is Under 1-Person Agency,")
("And Her Mother Will Be The CEO To Manage All Activities")
That is absolutely out of the question.
And why is that?
A film has a set story.
You think one can just change screen time...
to suit their own tastes?
Why not?
You think of this film...
as a work of art, don't you, Director?
But art is only art if it sells.
If it does not sell, what is it but trash?
Listen here, Yu Ji An's mother.
Let's think about this rationally.
In the current situation, whose name...
will help make this film a box office hit?
Han Yi Jin's first-ever leading role?
Or Yu Ji An's first comeback after her scandal?
- It would be Yu Ji An, wouldn't it? - Director Kang.
Come on, it is a fact.
The answer is already right there.
Why is he struggling with it so much?
Surely you are not using...
other people's money for your art...
just to satisfy your own ego, are you?
I cannot give you much time.
Let me know by tomorrow whether you...
are going to increase our Ji An's screen time...
or not.
Ha Yul's mom, you have a visitor.
Who is it?
Ji An, where are you?
Why are you not answering your phone?
I had something to take care of.
Why? Is something wrong?
How could you do this without even discussing it with me?
Why would I need to discuss it with you?
The outcome would have been the same even if I had discussed it.
This is Yi Jin's first leading role in the ten years since her debut.
- But to do this... - What business is that of yours?
Who on earth ruined you like this while I was gone?
I told you, didn't I?
Once your status is set, it is hard to change.
After everything I have done to get you to this point,
you are going to play second fiddle to the likes of Yi Jin?
Listen carefully.
If you want to live the rest of your life...
as the top star Yu Ji An,
stop caring about what other people feel.
Only think about yourself.
Everyone else is just your competition.
Hey, Yi Jin.
I heard from Director Kang.
This again? It is always the same with you.
- This is a misunderstanding... - A misunderstanding?
What misunderstanding?
You were always like this, even when we were idols.
If there was anything even slightly good,
be it an outfit, a song, or an opportunity,
you always snatched it away.
I thought you had changed a little, but...
I guess people do not change that easily, do they?
The money I gave Mi Jeong was really for her hospital bills.
The reason I was in touch with her...
was because I was trying to persuade her somehow.
And as for what happened with the CEO Noh...
You are right.
- I did it on purpose to screw you. - Han Yi Jin.
You always take what is mine without a second thought.
I absolutely despised you for it.
I wish you would just...
disappear from my life.
(Establishing the Rule of Law)
(J.An Entertainment)
(Ministry of Law)
(Kim Jun Sik)
("Yu Ji An is Under 1-Person Agency,")
("And Her Mother Will Be The CEO To Manage All Activities")
("Actress Yu Ji An Will Start Her Activities...")
A long-term exclusive contract?
You can't let that child dictate things forever.
If you do this one thing for me,
I'll entrust her entire management to you...
for the rest of Ji An's career in this industry.
You know how she is.
If I tell Ji An to die,
she's the kind of girl who would even pretend to.
So what are you asking to do?
To give you what you want,
I have to get what I want first.
Whatever it takes...
Make Ji An come back to me.
She lures in me minding my own business,
and makes a fool out of me.
And she thinks she can get a happy ending all by herself?
That would just be unfair to me.
Have you been well?
It's been a while, Mr. Cha. What brings you here?
I was wondering how Seon Woo was doing,
so I thought I'd stop by.
Please have a seat.
But I have a feeling Seon Woo is just an excuse,
and that you're really here to ask about someone else.
Is she doing all right?
Actually, I was just about to contact you...
about Ji An, Mr. Cha.
Is something wrong?
Something's off with Ji An.
She can't focus on set,
and her emotional scenes aren't what they used to be.
More than anything...
She seems very fragile.
To be honest,
because of the recent issue with her mother,
I wasn't feeling too great about Ji An either,
but now I just feel sorry for her.
I'm worried something might happen to her if she keeps this up.
I'm afraid.
I'm afraid she'll show up again and ruin my life.
I'm afraid I'll go back as the person I was.
- Hello. - Hello.
Of course.
There's no way he would be here.
(CEO Kim)
What's this about?
What?
What do you mean...
I heard you took good care of my Ji An...
by being her manager while I was gone.
As her mother, I'm grateful.
Not at all.
But you're not her manager anymore.
What I'm saying is...
Please refrain from actions...
that could give people the wrong idea,
like what you did earlier.
She just made her comeback.
It wouldn't be good for a scandal, would it?
Do you understand what I'm saying?
It seemed like Ji An was having a very hard time.
I appreciate your concern for my daughter,
but I'm here now, so stay out of it.
I'm afraid I can't do that.
I may not be her manager anymore,
but I am Yu Ji An's designated counsellor.
As a professional, I believe Ji An's condition...
is not something I can ignore.
So I plan on taking a very active interest from now on.
You're just like your father.
Starting with your looks,
all the way to your arrogant meddling...
in others' business.
Don't worry. Ji An doesn't know anything.
And of course, she should never find out.
If she were to find out,
there's no telling what she might do.
As her counsellor, you must know.
That she's more fragile than she appears.
In the past, she tried to hurt herself...
over something trivial.
She's that fragile.
If she finds out this secret,
what she might do...
is painfully obvious, isn't it?
You seem like a smart man,
so I trust you understand what I mean.
I told you about this ahead of time.
No, that's not it.
I'm not trying to change the concept.
Let's stick to the storyboard. But look. Look at the lighting.
- It's so plain. - No, the studio...
Director, if you want to elevate this,
please just listen to me.
If we add a bit more detail to the lighting...
Where have you been all this time?
I believe I told you I wasn't coming back here.
But you're here now. You came here on your own.
I had no other choice.
- I wonder why that is. - Cut.
Hey, Ji An. About your acting...
Let's take a quick break.
If you keep giving us this kind of schedule...
You mean, she has to focus on the filming all week...
once again in the second week of this month.
She'll be busy then, reviewing offers for a new project.
You ask for more screen time, but then say...
it's hard to cooperate with the filming schedule.
So what exactly do you expect me to do?
Why are you getting so upset?
We've already been considerate. This all happened because...
we had to revise the script to give her more screen time.
How much more accommodating do you want us to be?
- No. - I'll do it.
I said I'll do it. So both of you, please get out.
- Ji An. - I said I'll do it. Everyone stop.
Let's go.
("Yu Ji An's Another Abuse of Power Controversy Even After Comeback")
(If this keeps happening, maybe it's just her personality?)
(Don't the staff's stories seem more credible?)
("Yu Ji An's Another Abuse of Power Controversy Even After Comeback")
Mr. Cha.
Ji An...
I can't get in touch with her.
She's not on the second floor either.
This is driving me crazy.
Where could she have gone without her phone?
- When did you last hear from her? - Probably yesterday.
Then why are you only looking for her now?
I just thought she needed time alone to clear her head.
She's been through a lot lately.
Is there any place she might have gone?
She's always either at home or on set.
Don't tell me...
She's not thinking of doing something bad again, is she?
She was just like this before that happened.
Where are you going?
Something's off about Ji An.
She seems very fragile.
I'm starting to feel sorry for her.
I'm worried something might happen to her.
(1 dollar)
As her counsellor, you must know.
That she's more fragile than she appears.
In the past, she tried to hurt herself over something trivial.
(1 dollar)
Don't tell me...
She's not thinking of doing something bad again, is she?
She was just like this before that happened.
Yu Ji An.
Where in the world are you?
Please.
Actress Yu Ji An, who recently made...
a comeback after overcoming an abuse of power controversy,
is now embroiled in rumours that she has gone into hiding.
Reports say she has cancelled all her appointments...
and suddenly disappeared.
Her agency has issued a full denial,
claiming it is for health reasons.
However, due to recent false accusations...
and a series of incidents involving her,
there is growing concern for her safety...
on social media and in fan communities.
Does Eun Hwan know that you found out?
Not yet.
Good.
If you feel so sorry,
then leave Eun Hwan.
You two can never be together.
I don't think I need to tell you that anymore.
I don't want Eun Hwan...
to be hurt by that accident in any way.
You know what I mean, right?
Hey, hey. Did you see the news?
Did Yu Ji An really disappear?
Hey, disappearing would be better. What if it's...
Hey, watch what you say. It can't be that, right?
Anyway, the two of them fought a lot.
That's right. I heard that too.
Didn't she say she wished she would just disappear?
I wish you would just...
disappear from my life.
It was really harsh.
Hey, let's not just speculate among ourselves.
Right. It can't be that.
If it is, that would be crazy.
Stop drinking. You're going to ruin your health.
I think I'm being punished.
You idiot.
What do you have to be punished for?
I made her cry too often.
That beautiful woman.
When I think about it,
I never really gave her anything.
I always held back.
I always held back expressing my feelings and smiling.
I was afraid that I might get too greedy.
I was also afraid I wouldn't be able to handle myself.
So I always kept my distance.
And that always...
made her cry.
If I had known I'd regret it this much,
I should have given her everything instead of holding back.
I'm sure she's okay.
Don't worry.
I will find her no matter what.
I'll find her,
and this time,
I'll protect her for sure.
(Let's eat Americano after getting an attendance stamp.)
(1 dollar)
- You're not hurt? - No.
Then I'm glad about that.
Right now, I'm about to do the most selfish thing...
in my life.
(Scene in the Police Station, Day)
(Scene in the House, Night)
I'm afraid.
I'm afraid she'll show up again and ruin my life.
I'm afraid I'll go back as the person I was.
If that happens,
I'll protect you.
I was wrong.
So please...
Please stop torturing me and just show up.
If you just show up,
I'll keep my promise this time.
Please.
(Woo Dong Gyeong)
- Hello. - Hey, I remember now.
It's the fishing spot.
Dong Gyeong, do you know where that is?
Where?
The place where Eun Hwan ran off to.
I was the one who told her about it.
Why are you just telling me this now?
Eun Hwan?
How did you know I was here?
This is the best place you could run away to?
How anticlimactic.
I was ready to find you at the ends of the earth.
You missed me a lot, didn't you?
You're lying.
I really missed you.
I'm sorry for leaving you alone.
I'm also sorry for not protecting you.
I'm really...
I'm so sorry.
(Receipt)
This is for one week's stay?
No way. It's not like this is a hotel suite.
Tell me about it.
She comes to a guesthouse in the countryside and what? What?
- What? - How many times...
do I have to say it, ma'am?
Amenities.
Gosh.
Anyway, amenities or whatever.
I've never met anyone looking for things like that.
Not only that,
she showed up without a penny to her name.
Including food and clothes, she owes me over 1,000 dollars.
Don't you know it costs a lot to maintain a star's image?
- What was that? - What? What did I do?
I think you just thought, "Did I make a mistake coming here?"
- I felt it. - No, that's ridiculous...
You said you were sorry,
but now you're being so petty about money.
I'm telling you, that's not it.
You just thought that a second ago.
That's absolutely not true. This is so unfair.
That's not it. Why would I think like that?
If you think it's a waste, then just leave.
Why would I leave? I came here for you, Ji An.
Then pay for it.
Why did you run away to a fishing spot...
despite you can't even fish?
I just wanted to run away,
but I didn't know where to go.
And I was also curious about a place you had memories of.
Have things been hard for you?
It was my mom.
She's the one who put CEO Kim up to the abuse of power controversy.
I know, right? Shocking, isn't it?
I couldn't believe it when I heard it.
Are you okay?
She must have thought I'd come running back to her...
if I was struggling.
But too bad for her.
Because now,
I don't think I can put up with her anymore.
This time...
I'll be right by your side.
(Contract Termination Notice)
(Reason: Breach of Trust)
What is this?
It's exactly what it looks like.
I'm terminating all contracts between you and me.
From now on, you have no rights over me.
You're still acting like a child.
If you're having such a hard time, take a few more days off.
I'll take care of your schedule...
Soon, I'll be filing a lawsuit to nullify the contracts...
- you signed without my consent. - You little...
Are you saying you're fine with Cha Eun Hwan finding out the truth?
Is it okay if he knows about why his father died...
and who was responsible for his death?
Do you really think I wouldn't remember anything?
What's there to be scared of?
Just go inside the storage room for a little while.
They said you can be the protagonist.
But I'm still scared.
You don't want to live with me?
Ji An, if we want to live together, we need a house.
You can do it, right?
Let's go.
A while ago, CEO Kim sent me something...
as an apology gift.
Do you want to hear it?
(Call Recording)
To give you what you want,
I have to get what I want first.
- How... - She has to learn...
how tough it is,
so she'll miss my embrace, don't you think?
Push Ji An to rock bottom.
As far as you possibly can.
Ji An, this is all fabricated.
- Like you did to me? - Me? It was for your own good.
In order to protect you, I had to...
keep you by my side.
No parent would destroy their own child...
in order to protect them.
Ji An.
I...
- I did it for... - I will no longer...
destroy myself...
just to be loved by you.
Are you okay?
She probably left him...
because she loved him.
You're awake?
How are you feeling?
Will you go somewhere with me?
(The Late Cha Woo Seok)
If you get scared or feel like you're in danger,
just scream for help.
And I'll come running like Superman to save you.
Got it?
I'm so sorry it took me so long to come.
Sir.
How long have you known?
Not for long.
My memory came back on that last rainy day.
Then why didn't you say anything?
Because I thought if you knew that I knew,
it would be too hard on you, Eun Hwan.
I've grown up a lot, haven't I?
Why...
didn't you hate me?
If it hadn't been for me,
your father...
and sister...
wouldn't have ended up that way.
How could I hate you?
Even when you couldn't remember anything,
you could never let go of the guilt...
and were always in pain.
My heart always went out to you.
So,
you don't have to feel sorry anymore.
That incident was...
no one's...
fault.
It was just an accident.
My father...
wouldn't want you to suffer like this either, Ji An.
You can do that for me, can't you?
We...
can't be together, can we?
Still, I'm glad...
that we can say goodbye in such a beautiful place.
Thank you.
Thanks to you,
I learned how to understand someone...
and how to love someone.
Thank you too...
for coming into my life...
and letting me know how brightly...
I could smile.
(1 Year Later)
(Best Supporting Actress: Yu Ji An)
(March Individual Brand Reputation: Number 1)
("Yu Ji An, Best Supporting Actress at Yeongjong Film Awards")
(Only Yu Ji An could play Jung In.)
(She deserves this.)
Yes.
Mr. Cha, it's almost time for your lecture.
Oh, yes.
(What is "Empathy?")
(About True Empathy in This Era)
Everyone,
what is empathy?
When we say we're empathizing, we often try to explain things...
or solve the problem.
But that's not what empathy is.
It's something you can feel just by being there for someone.
The foundation of my method acting is empathy.
If you don't understand the character's feelings...
and just go through the motions,
that's an insult to the acting.
You saw how my acting improved overnight, didn't you?
What's the secret? Repeat after me. Empathy.
Empathy.
That's right. You have to act with your heart.
Why won't anyone believe me?
I know. I know...
what I did was wrong.
I only did it because I was so scared that day.
Just once,
couldn't you try to understand how I was feeling?
Ha Yul.
Mom.
- Have you been having fun? - Yes.
Did you go on the slide a lot? How many times?
- Hello. Here you are. - Thank you.
You can go up to the second floor now.
(Cha Song Hwan Solo Exhibition: After-image And Reality)
- Thank you. - Welcome.
- Congratulations. - Thanks for coming. You're busy.
- Thank you. - I came with a friend.
These are amazing.
You made it.
What do you think of the exhibition?
It's great. You did a good job.
Do you still contact to Ji An?
No.
You know tomorrow is the anniversary of Dad's death, right?
I guess it'll be hard for you to make it.
So I'll have to go alone, right?
I'm sorry, Eun Hwan.
Even though I knew my unhappiness wasn't your fault,
back then, I needed someone to blame...
just to get through it.
I really wanted to apologise to you.
And...
to Ji An too.
I think...
this answer is enough.
Have a good visit to meet Dad tomorrow.
(The Late Cha Woo Seok)
No way.
There's no way I can feel this.
It's been over for ages.
Yu Ji An.
Where on earth are you?
Please.
Just appear in front of me.